<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mapathon on OpenStreetMap Kerala</title><link>https://kerala.openstreetmap.in/tags/mapathon/</link><description>Recent content in Mapathon on OpenStreetMap Kerala</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 10:34:54 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kerala.openstreetmap.in/tags/mapathon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Building OSM Kerala Community</title><link>https://kerala.openstreetmap.in/building-osm-kerala-community/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 10:34:54 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://kerala.openstreetmap.in/building-osm-kerala-community/</guid><description>Building OSM Kerala Community OpenStreetMap was founded by Steve Coast in 2004, in focus to create a Free and Open collaborative editable mapping platform for all like wikipedia. In 2006 Openstreet map foundation was established to encourage the growth, development and distribution of free geospatial data.
Before Kerala Flood Events https://wiki.openstreetmap.org/wiki/Kerala/Events
NITC mapping party - October 23-24, 2009 This is the first OSM Mapping Party documented in Kerala, held at National Institute of Technology Calicut.</description></item><item><title>Intelligent Property Management System; Webinar Participation Report</title><link>https://kerala.openstreetmap.in/activities/ipms-webinar-oct-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kerala.openstreetmap.in/activities/ipms-webinar-oct-2020/</guid><description>Report of event participation Event was jointly organised by KILA and ULTS. Joy Elaman (KILA director) briefed about the importance of GIS and welcomed the participants. Dr Harilal inaugurated the event and briefed about the history of GIS in Kerala.
Nizamuddin (Kerala landuse board and KSREC) gave a demo on (https://kattakadalac.com/). Project has collected lot of data in that LAC. He also explained plans of expanding that project. When asked about releasing that as opendata, there was no response in the chat.</description></item><item><title>Mapathon Keralam and OpenStreetMap Community Collaboration</title><link>https://kerala.openstreetmap.in/mapathon-keralam-osm-community-statement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 17:53:58 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://kerala.openstreetmap.in/mapathon-keralam-osm-community-statement/</guid><description>Mapathon Keralam and OpenStreetMap Community Collaboration This is the letter to Director Kerala IT Mission, behalf of the OpenStreetMap India Community on 14 September 2020 (PDF)
Dear Smt. Chithra,
We are writing this letter on behalf of the OpenStreetMap India Community. We are part of the global OpenStreetMapmovement and have a history of mapping country for over 15 years. Our community members are spread acrossIndia, representing its vast geographic and cultural diversity.</description></item></channel></rss>